<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<guides>
    <guide>
        <id>1</id>
        <name>Upload a campaign</name>
        <description>How to upload your campaigns to Ad Auction Dashboard</description>
        <steps>
            <step>Make sure you have your log files available. You should have a log file for clicks, impressions and server.</step>
            <link>
                <linkText>Click here to read more about your log files</linkText>
                <linkRef>2</linkRef>
            </link>
            <step>Select "Upload Campaign" from the main menu</step>
            <step>Enter your campaign's name</step>
            <step>Upload each of your log files by clicking on the labelled boxes</step>
            <step>Hit "Submit"</step>
            <step>If successful, you will be directed back to the main menu</step>
            <step>If unsuccessful, refer to the error message on screen and try again</step>
        </steps>
    </guide>
    <guide>
        <id>2</id>
        <name>Log files</name>
        <description>Understanding your campaign's data</description>
        <sections>
            <section>
                <sectionName>Clicks</sectionName>
                <sectionText>This log file is for all instances in which an ad was clicked on by a user. For each click we know the time, what user clicked on it, and how much that click costed.</sectionText>
            </section>
            <section>
                <sectionName>Impressions</sectionName>
                <sectionText>Each impression is someone viewing your ad regardless of whether they interact with it. For each impression we know the time and that user's gender (Male/Female), age bracket, income (Low/Medium/High), the context in which they saw the ad (Blog, News, etc.), and how much that impression cost.</sectionText>
            </section>
            <section>
                <sectionName>Server</sectionName>
                <sectionText>This log file is used to track a user's interactions after clicking on an ad. For each instance we can see the time in which they entered and exited the website, how many pages they viewed and whether a user acts on the ad (e.g.by buying a product)</sectionText>
            </section>
        </sections>
    </guide>
    <guide>
        <id>3</id>
        <name>Adding Filters</name>
        <description>How to add filters to your loaded campaign</description>
        <steps>
            <step>Select "Load Campaign" from the main menu</step>
            <step>Select the campaign you wish to load into the system</step>
            <step>Select the filters tab in the bottom left</step>
            <step>Choose the filters you want to apply</step>
            <step>E.g. Unchecking the boxes for "Male" and "High" and picking a "Before" date</step>
            <step>An updated graph will now be displayed</step>
        </steps>
    </guide>
    <guide>
        <id>4</id>
        <name>Change between metrics</name>
        <description>How to change between metrics for your loaded campaign</description>
        <steps>
            <step>Select "Load Campaign" from the main menu</step>
            <step>Select the campaign you wish to load into the system</step>
            <step>Select the metrics tab in the bottom left</step>
            <step>Choose the metrics you wish to look at (E.g. "Number of Impressions" or "Number of Clicks")</step>
            <step>An updated graph will now be displayed</step>
        </steps>
    </guide>
    <guide>
        <id>5</id>
        <name>Change type of graph</name>
        <description>How to change type of graph for your loaded campaign</description>
        <steps>
            <step>Select "Load Campaign" from the main menu</step>
            <step>Select the campaign you wish to load into the system</step>
            <step>Select the drop down button in the top right</step>
            <step>Choose the between the available graphs (E.g. "Cumulative" or "Trend")</step>
            <step>An updated graph will now be displayed</step>
        </steps>
    </guide>
    <guide>
        <id>6</id>
        <name>Switch between graph and dashboard</name>
        <description>How to switch between graph and dashboard for your loaded campaign</description>
        <steps>
            <step>Select "Load Campaign" from the main menu</step>
            <step>Select the campaign you wish to load into the system</step>
            <step>If currently displaying graphs, click the Dashboard button on the top right</step>
            <step>A dashboard will now be displayed</step>
            <step>If currently displaying dashboard, Click the Graph button on the top right</step>
            <step>An updated graph will now be displayed</step>
        </steps>
    </guide>
</guides>